tuugo.in 2017-06-06

# Tuugo Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us, so Tuugo has created this Privacy Policy to explain how your information is protected, collected and used. Tuugo is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

This Privacy Policy applies to all Tuugo web sites, including our publicly accessible web sites located at Tuugo.com ("Tuugo").

This Privacy Policy is effective since 06/2013

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time. By using Tuugo, you consent to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and are aware that our policies may evolve in the future. If there is a conflict between our Terms of Use governing your use of the Site and this Privacy Policy, the Terms of Use will prevail.

Table of Contents:

**01\. Collection**

**02\. Use**

**03\. Disclosure**

**04\. Using Information from Tuugo**

**05\. Access, Modification, and Deletion**

**06\. Security**

**07\. Cookies**

**08\. Third-party links**

**09\. For California Residents Only**

**10\. General**

**01\. Collection.**

Information posted on Tuugo is obviously publicly available. Our servers are located in the United States and in the European Union. Therefore, if you choose to provide us your personal information, you are consenting to the transfer and storage of that information onto our servers on the United States and Europe.

We collect information from you when you:

\- Register into our site  
\- Fill out a form  
\- Respond to our surveys  
\- Subscribe to our newsletter

We collect and store the following personal information: 

\- name, email address, mailing address, phone number, and (depending on the service used) financial information;   
\- computer sign-on data, statistics on page views, traffic to and from Tuugo and listing data (all through cookies – see Cookies section);   
-demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests  
\- other information, including users IP address and standard web log information.

You may, however, visit our site anonymously

**02\. Use.**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

\- To personalize your experience, and to understand your needs and provide you with a better service;  
\- To improve our website, we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you;  
\- To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature;  
\- Resolve disputes, collect fees, and solve troubleshooting issues;   
\- Encourage safe trading and enforce our policies;  
\- To improve customer service, your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs;  
\- Customize users’ experience, measure interest in our services, and inform users about services and updates;   
\- Communicate marketing and promotional offers to users;   
\- The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions;  
\- Do other things for users as described when we collect the information. 

**03\. Disclosure.**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, corporate affiliates who help detect and prevent potentially illegal acts and provide joint services (our corporate affiliates will market only to users who ask them to), or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, respond to claims that a posting or other content violates other’s rights, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**04\. Using Information from Tuugo.**

You may use personal information gathered from Tuugo only to contact another user about a specific posting, not to send spam or collect personal information from someone who hasn’t agreed to that.

Please see our Terms of Use regarding this matter.

**05\. Access, Modification, and Deletion.**

You can see, modify or erase your personal information by reviewing your posting or account status page, or deleting it from the control panel.

Contact customer support (supporttuugo.com) if you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

There may a charge associated with such requests but these will not exceed the amounts permitted by law. We delete personal information when we no longer need it for the purposes we described earlier. We retain personal information as permitted by law to resolve disputes, enforce our policies; and prevent misuse from third users or companies.

**06\. Security.**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

We use a great amount of tools (encryption, passwords, physical security) to protect your personal information, and do our best effort on it, but in case of hacking, corruption of files, and other mishappenings, we do not make guarantees. 

**07\. Cookies.**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. 

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. 

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**08\. Third-party links.**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**09\. For California Residents Only.**

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the 'Edit Profile' page.

**10\. General.**

We may update this policy at any time, with updates taking effect at the next update of the policy or after 30 days, whichever is sooner. If we or our corporate affiliates are involved in a merge or acquisition, we may share personal information with another company, but this policy will continue to apply. 

Send questions about this policy to legalTuugo.com.
